const thorQuiz = [
    
    {
        question: "What is the name of Thor's enchanted hammer?",
        choice1: "Might Hammer",
        choice2: "Asgaurd",
        choice3: "Mjolnir",
        choice4: "Fenris",
        answer: 3,
         },

     
        {
            question: "Who is Thors Father?" ,
            choice1: "Odin",
            choice2: "Loki",
            choice3: "Zeus",
            choice4: "Asgaurd",
            answer: 1,
        },

        {
            question: "Who was the first Marvel character to lift Thors Hammer",
            choice1: "Antman",
            choice2: "Winter Soldier",
            choice3: "Captain America",
            choice4: "Black Widow",
            answer: 3,
        },

        {
            question: "What is the Name of Thors Love interest?",
            choice1: "Sharon Carter",
            choice2: "May Forever",
            choice3: "June Forester",
            choice4: "Jane Foster",
            answer: 4,
        },


        {
            question: "Where does Thor live",
            choice1: "Earth",
            choice2: "Asgaurd",
            choice3: "Moon",
            choice4: "Jupiter",
            answer: 2,
        },


        {
            question: "What was foretold to be the end of Asgard",
            choice1: "Ragnorak",
            choice2: "The End!",
            choice3: "Time Crush",
            choice4: "Mjolnir",
            answer: 4,
        },


        {
            question:"Thor also had an axe what was the name of it?",
            choice1: "Storm Bringer",
            choice2: "War Bringer",
            choice3: "Storm Breaker",
            choice4: "Mighty Axe",
            answer: 2,
        },


        {
            question: "Finish this saying 'Whosoever holds this hammer, if they be worthy'",
            choice1: "Shall have Glory",
            choice2: "Shall have Great power",
            choice3: "Shall possess the power of Thor",
            choice4: "Shall have Ritches",
            answer: 3,
        },


        {
            question: "What was Thors sisters name?",
            choice1: "Hela",
            choice2: "Helen",
            choice3: "Jane",
            choice4: "June",
            answer: 1,
        },


        {
            question: "Which Actor Plays Thor?",
            choice1: "Chris Hemsworth",
            choice2: "Noel King",
            choice3: "Chris Carter",
            choice4: "Tony Howard",
            answer: 1,
        },


        {
            question: "Which Villan destroyed Asgaurd",
            choice1: "Surtur",
            choice2: "Satan",
            choice3: "Smog",
            choice4: "Ice King",
            answer: 1,
        },


        {
            question: "What Nickname Does Stark Give To Thor?",
            choice1: "Hammer Head",
            choice2: "Point Break",
            choice3: "Lazy Viking",
            choice4: "Lightening Face",
            answer: 2,
        },

        {
            question: "Who Controls The Bifrost?",
            choice1: "Balder",
            choice2: "Vidar",
            choice3: "Heimdall",
            choice4: "Loki",
            answer: 3,
        },

        {
            question: "What Does Thor Call Rocket?",
            choice1: "Rabbit",
            choice2: "Squirrel",
            choice3: "Chipmonk",
            choice4: "Fox",
            answer: 1,
        },

        {
            question: "Who Is The Leader Of The Frost Giants?",
            choice1: "Loki",
            choice2: "Hail Strum",
            choice3: "Raze",
            choice4: "Laufey",
            answer: 4,
        },

        {
            question: "Which character is Thor's half brother?",
            choice1: "Laufey",
            choice2: "Heimdall",
            choice3: "Loki",
            choice4: "Balder",
            answer: 3,
        },

        {
            question: "What is the Asgardian name for the Earthly plane?",
            choice1: "Hela",
            choice2: "Midgard",
            choice3: "Valhalla",
            choice4: "Ragnorak",
            answer: 2,
        },

        {
            question: "What is the Asgardian world tree called?",
            choice1: "Hela",
            choice2: "Tree of Life",
            choice3: "Yggdrasil",
            choice4: "Hela",
            answer: 3,
        },

        {
            question: "What animals pull Thor's chariot?",
            choice1: "Rabbits",
            choice2: "Goats",
            choice3: "Bulls",
            choice4: "Pigs",
            answer: 2,
        },


        {
            question: "Thor was a founding member of what superhero team?",
            choice1: "Hela",
            choice2: "Time Keepers",
            choice3: "Gaurdians",
            choice4: "Avengers",
            answer: 4,
        },






 
]